<div class="col-lg-10 s_table_of_content_main oe_structure oe_empty o_colored_level" data-name="Content" data-editor-message-default="true" data-editor-message="DRAG BUILDING BLOCKS HERE">
                    <section class="pb16 o_colored_level" style="background-image: none;">

                        <div class="text-center wow fadeInUp" data-wow-delay="0.1s">
                            <h6 class="section-title bg-white text-center text-primary px-3">About Us</h6>
                            <h2 class="mb-5" id="table_of_content_heading_1725893044400_59" data-anchor="true">Mary Immaculate English Medium School</h2>
                        </div>

                        <h2 id="table_of_content_heading_1725893044401_60" data-anchor="true">About Us</h2>
                        <p>
                            Mary Immaculate E.M. School, Basirhat was started on 11 March 2014 at OMI
                            Maria Bhavan, with KG 1 as a co-education school to be upgraded every year.
                            The school was accorded with permanent NOC eum Certificate of Recognition,
                            Refer, Memo No. 20- SC/AIS/NOC AIS/RTE/COMMTT/55/2019, dated: 24.01.2023 by
                            the Directorate of School Education, Government of West Bengal. The school follows
                            the proposed syllabus of ICSE Board, New Delhi. "Mary Immaculate English Medium School",
                            Basirhat, is a missionary school, which has its mission and vision according to the Gospel values. We take care of our children's all-round education.
                        </p>
                        <p>
                            We are fortunate and blessed with a team of committed teachers and non-teaching staff.
                            Our parents are a strong support to participate harmoniously to create an educational
                            experience to anyone in the campus by their dynamic activities with the school staff.
                            Anyone can witness a variety of activities that keep the class rooms dynamic and cheerful
                            learning hubs of Mary Immaculate School campus.
                        </p>
                    </section>
                    <section class="pb16 o_colored_level" style="background-image: none;">
                        <h2 id="table_of_content_heading_1725893044402_61" data-anchor="true">OBLATES</h2>
                        <h4 class="text-center">A heart as big as the world.</h4>
                        <p>
                            Eugene de Mazenod was born into a noble family of Aix-en-Provence
                            in southern France in 1782, but his family had to flee as refugees
                            during the French Revolution. In 1802 he returned to France and embraced a
                            frivolous social life. However, on Good Friday 1807, before the crucifix in a
                            church in Aix, the young man experienced a profound conversion that made him
                            understand the spiritual and material plight of France and the Church. Within a year he entered the seminary and was ordained in 1811.
                        </p>
                        <h4>Professional themes</h4>
                        <p>
                            Father de Mazenod set about rebuilding a world of Christian values. He preached
                            in villages with passion, tirelessly bringing the Word of God and the sacraments
                            to all, visiting prisoners and offering the poor a renewed sense of dignity. In 1816
                            other priests, inspired by his vision and energy, joined him and in 1826 the Missionary
                            Oblates of Mary Immaculate was formally approved by Pope Leo XII. De Mazenod, deemed to
                            have had a heart as big as the world', sent his growing corps of Oblates to mission in Canada,
                            Sri Lanka, South Africa and in various parts of Europe.
                        </p>
                        <br>
                        <p>
                            Bishop Eugene de Mazenod died on May 21, 1861 and the Church recognised his life of dedication,
                            virtue and outreach to the most abandoned when, on December 3, 1995. Pope John Paul 11 officially
                            declared him a saint. More than 3,700 Oblate priests and brothers, supported by many Oblate Lay Associates,
                            continue to mission on every continent of the world. His charism lives on in them.
                        </p>
                    </section>
                    <section class="pb16">
                        <h2 id="table_of_content_heading_1725893044403_62" data-anchor="true">OMI and Education</h2>
                        <h4 class="text-center">A heart as big as the world.</h4>
                        <p>
                            The Society of Oblates of Mary Immaculate, a Catholic Christian Religious Order
                            founded by Saint Eugene de Mazenod in 1816, has been active in the field of education
                            throughout the world since its origin. Worldwide, the Oblates are responsible for 86
                            Educational Institutions in 63 countries. These Oblates Educational Institutions
                            engage the efforts of approximately 1000's of teachers, educating approximately 30,000 students.
                            In India, The Society of Oblates has founded 18 Primary and Middle Schools, 18 High Schools with 215
                            teachers, educating about 5000 students belonging to every social class, community, and linguistic
                            group. These Institutions are part of the Catholic Church's effort to share in the country's
                            educational undertaking. The Oblate School in India aims at the intellectual, integral,
                            personal formation of the children and youth. To accomplish these, special efforts are made:
                        </p>
                        <h4>Professional themes</h4>
                        <p>
                            Father de Mazenod set about rebuilding a world of Christian values. He preached
                            in villages with passion, tirelessly bringing the Word of God and the sacraments
                            to all, visiting prisoners and offering the poor a renewed sense of dignity. In 1816
                            other priests, inspired by his vision and energy, joined him and in 1826 the Missionary
                            Oblates of Mary Immaculate was formally approved by Pope Leo XII. De Mazenod, deemed to
                            have had a heart as big as the world', sent his growing corps of Oblates to mission in Canada,
                            Sri Lanka, South Africa and in various parts of Europe.
                        </p>
                        <br>
                        <p>
                            Bishop Eugene de Mazenod died on May 21, 1861 and the Church recognised his life of dedication,
                            virtue and outreach to the most abandoned when, on December 3, 1995. Pope John Paul 11 officially
                            declared him a saint. More than 3,700 Oblate priests and brothers, supported by many Oblate Lay Associates,
                            continue to mission on every continent of the world. His charism lives on in them.
                        </p>
                    </section>
                </div>